[{"name":"Popeye's Kitchen","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411798065,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"demon-blue"},{"x":55,"y":15,"type":"ghost-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":18,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":60,"y":18,"width":21,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":1,"y":14}},{"name":"Popeye's Chicken","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411763183,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":14,"type":"ghost-blue"},{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"demon-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":64,"y":18,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":31,"y":18,"width":9,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":14}},{"name":"Vienna Shopping Center","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411626333,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":4,"type":"demon-blue"},{"x":76,"y":14,"type":"ghost-cyan"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":55,"y":18,"width":26,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":63,"y":13,"width":18,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":71,"y":8,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":8,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":4}},{"name":"Elevation","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411763246,"enemies":[{"x":6,"y":2,"type":"dwer"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":6,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":18,"y":10,"width":13,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":64,"y":22,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":47,"y":6,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":33,"y":6,"width":12,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":1,"y":2}},{"name":"The Seven Dwers","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411667552,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"dwer"},{"x":69,"y":19,"type":"dwer"},{"x":62,"y":19,"type":"dwer"},{"x":55,"y":19,"type":"dwer"},{"x":48,"y":19,"type":"dwer"},{"x":41,"y":19,"type":"dwer"},{"x":34,"y":19,"type":"dwer"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":15,"y":18,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":72,"y":18,"width":9,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":14}},{"name":"The Tomb of King James III","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411667939,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":8,"type":"ghost-king"},{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"ghost-green"},{"x":76,"y":14,"type":"ghost-cyan"},{"x":56,"y":3,"type":"ghost-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":11,"y":18,"width":70,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":21,"y":13,"width":60,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":31,"y":7,"width":50,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":3}},{"name":"The Parking Lot","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411706574,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"demon-blue"},{"x":1,"y":19,"type":"moped"},{"x":39,"y":8,"type":"ghost-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":18,"width":13,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":68,"y":18,"width":13,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":35,"y":18,"width":13,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":14,"y":12,"width":54,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":35,"y":7,"width":13,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":39,"y":19},"door":{"x":39,"y":3}},{"name":"Moped Madness","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411671247,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":3,"type":"moped"},{"x":13,"y":11,"type":"moped"},{"x":76,"y":14,"type":"ghost-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":15,"width":45,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":7,"width":28,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":70,"y":18,"width":11,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":76,"y":19},"door":{"x":1,"y":19}},{"name":"Maple Avenue","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411768238,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":15,"type":"ghost-green"},{"x":1,"y":2,"type":"ghost-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":76,"y":6,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":67,"y":22,"width":9,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":22,"width":9,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":14,"width":9,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":520,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":10,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":2}},{"name":"Jerf Clertern","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411763234,"enemies":[{"x":39,"y":19,"type":"jerf"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":11,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":70,"y":23,"width":11,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":17,"y":23,"width":48,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":17,"y":22,"width":3,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":62,"y":22,"width":3,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":16,"width":11,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":19}},{"name":"The Telegards","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411763238,"enemies":[{"x":57,"y":14,"type":"telegard-gray"},{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"telegard-gray"},{"x":1,"y":2,"type":"telegard-gray"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":22,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":515,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":30,"y":23,"width":51,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":515,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":30,"y":22,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":515,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":55,"y":18,"width":26,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":515,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":55,"y":17,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":515,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":6,"width":37,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":515,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":14}},{"name":"Flowing Through the Sewing","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411800605,"enemies":[{"x":7,"y":2,"type":"ghost-cyan"},{"x":55,"y":8,"type":"ghost-cyan"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":6,"y":2,"width":1,"height":17,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":22,"y":6,"width":1,"height":17,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":38,"y":2,"width":1,"height":17,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":62,"y":22,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":16,"y":22,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":48,"y":22,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":62,"y":7,"width":11,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":62,"y":3,"width":1,"height":4,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":62,"y":2,"width":19,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":70,"y":12,"width":11,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":54,"y":12,"width":1,"height":11,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":2},"door":{"x":63,"y":3}},{"name":"Escalation","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411876011,"enemies":[{"x":75,"y":7,"type":"ghost-green"},{"x":1,"y":2,"type":"ghost-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":39,"y":2,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":true,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15},{"x":45,"y":6,"width":29,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":75,"y":15,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":75,"y":11}},{"name":"The Jerkbots","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411876412,"enemies":[{"x":42,"y":14,"type":"robot-blue"},{"x":68,"y":19,"type":"robot-cyan"},{"x":1,"y":19,"type":"robot-cyan"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":32,"y":18,"width":15,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":518,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":37,"y":19},"door":{"x":37,"y":14}},{"name":"The Jerf Box","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411876781,"enemies":[{"x":57,"y":19,"type":"jerf"},{"x":50,"y":19,"type":"jerf"},{"x":43,"y":19,"type":"jerf"},{"x":36,"y":19,"type":"jerf"},{"x":29,"y":19,"type":"jerf"},{"x":22,"y":19,"type":"jerf"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":20,"y":13,"width":2,"height":10,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":62,"y":13,"width":2,"height":10,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":71,"y":9,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15},{"x":15,"y":22,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":19}},{"name":"High Dive","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411877413,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":10,"type":"ghost-green"}],"platforms":[{"x":17,"y":19,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":1,"y":23,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":36,"y":14,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":66,"y":5,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":72,"y":23,"width":9,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":52,"y":9,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":72,"y":19}},{"name":"The Rectal Probers","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411877951,"enemies":[{"x":16,"y":14,"type":"alien-blue"},{"x":55,"y":14,"type":"alien-cyan"},{"x":71,"y":19,"type":"alien-green"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":11,"y":18,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":31,"y":18,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":50,"y":18,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":19}},{"name":"Spidy Breaks an Alien","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411879039,"enemies":[{"x":71,"y":19,"type":"alien-green"},{"x":30,"y":14,"type":"alien-cyan"},{"x":73,"y":2,"type":"alien-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":28,"y":18,"width":43,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":28,"y":17,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":69,"y":17,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":48,"y":6,"width":33,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":19}},{"name":"The Flight of the Chicken","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411879704,"enemies":[],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":12,"y":23,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":37,"y":14,"width":15,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":68,"y":17,"width":13,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":13}},{"name":"The Ghost of Samos","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411880914,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":19,"type":"ghost-green"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":20,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":523,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":31,"y":23,"width":16,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":523,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":57,"y":23,"width":24,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":523,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":76,"y":6,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":523,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":71,"y":6,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":523,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":16,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":2}},{"name":"The Revenge of King James III","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411881257,"enemies":[{"x":65,"y":11,"type":"ghost-king"},{"x":43,"y":2,"type":"ghost-king"},{"x":1,"y":9,"type":"ghost-king"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":26,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":522,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":40,"y":23,"width":41,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":522,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":27,"y":23,"width":13,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":514,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":49,"y":10,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":522,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":49,"y":6}},{"name":"Glyndon Street","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411881635,"enemies":[{"x":26,"y":11,"type":"moped"}],"platforms":[{"x":24,"y":15,"width":37,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":519,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":24,"y":14,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":519,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":59,"y":14,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":519,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":519,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":19,"y":22,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":519,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":61,"y":2,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":519,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":41,"y":11}},{"name":"Discount DVDs, Try Before you Buy","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411881951,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":2,"type":"demon-green"},{"x":76,"y":2,"type":"demon-green"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":6,"width":30,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":524,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":51,"y":6,"width":30,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":524,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":31,"y":6,"width":20,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":524,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":29,"y":7,"width":2,"height":9,"ch":"Û","attr":524,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":524,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":1,"y":17,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":524,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":38,"y":2},"door":{"x":1,"y":13}},{"name":"Jerf versus the Liberal Scum","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411882558,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":19,"type":"jerf"},{"x":15,"y":19,"type":"jerf"},{"x":62,"y":19,"type":"jerf"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":38,"y":6,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":38,"y":19},"door":{"x":38,"y":2}},{"name":"High Dive II: The Wrath of Jerf","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411883488,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"jerf"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":11,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":21,"y":19,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":40,"y":15,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":49,"y":11,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":58,"y":23,"width":23,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":58,"y":22,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":58,"y":7,"width":7,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":60,"y":19}},{"name":"A Matter of Timing","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411884134,"enemies":[{"x":35,"y":11,"type":"ghost-cyan"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":20,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":21,"y":23,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":26,"y":6,"width":2,"height":18,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":47,"y":6,"width":2,"height":18,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":35,"y":23,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1},{"x":28,"y":2,"width":7,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":513,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.1}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":35,"y":19}},{"name":"Lester versus the Documentation","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411960372,"enemies":[{"x":13,"y":19,"type":"lester"},{"x":31,"y":8,"type":"ghost-green"},{"x":42,"y":19,"type":"lester"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":80,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":11,"y":6,"width":2,"height":17,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":6,"y":22,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":69,"y":6,"width":2,"height":17,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":76,"y":6,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":71,"y":11,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":76,"y":16,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":68,"y":6,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":63,"y":22,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":19}},{"name":"Sacrosanct Configurations","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411961510,"enemies":[{"x":56,"y":2,"type":"lester"},{"x":12,"y":2,"type":"lester"},{"x":53,"y":19,"type":"lester"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":71,"y":23,"width":10,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":true,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":38,"y":23,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":11,"y":18,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":33,"y":18,"width":15,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15},{"x":11,"y":14,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":11,"y":10,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":12,"y":14,"width":15,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15},{"x":11,"y":6,"width":51,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":11,"y":5,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":61,"y":5,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":48,"y":23,"width":16,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":48,"y":22,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":63,"y":22,"width":1,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":517,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":2},"door":{"x":38,"y":19}},{"name":"The Outskirts of Observation","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411961938,"enemies":[{"x":76,"y":13,"type":"ghost-red"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":23,"width":16,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":33,"y":23,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":64,"y":23,"width":17,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":521,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[{"x":32,"y":20,"type":"flighttime"}],"player":{"x":1,"y":19},"door":{"x":76,"y":19}},{"name":"The Periphery of Perception","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411962286,"enemies":[{"x":8,"y":7,"type":"ghost-red"},{"x":76,"y":14,"type":"ghost-red"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":6,"width":15,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":52,"y":23,"width":29,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":34,"y":12,"width":6,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":516,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[{"x":8,"y":3,"type":"flighttime"}],"player":{"x":1,"y":2},"door":{"x":76,"y":19}},{"name":"The Cusp of Consciousness","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411962529,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":14,"type":"ghost-red"},{"x":76,"y":7,"type":"ghost-cyan"},{"x":43,"y":19,"type":"robot-cyan"},{"x":56,"y":19,"type":"demon-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":67,"y":6,"width":14,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":514,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":1,"y":11,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":514,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15},{"x":24,"y":23,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":514,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":41,"y":23,"width":40,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":514,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15},{"x":41,"y":22,"width":2,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":514,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":76,"y":2},"door":{"x":24,"y":19}},{"name":"The Center of Awareness","time":60,"author":"Echicken","system":"bbs/loveclown","date":1411962686,"enemies":[{"x":1,"y":7,"type":"ghost-red"},{"x":76,"y":11,"type":"ghost-red"},{"x":37,"y":15,"type":"ghost-red"},{"x":1,"y":19,"type":"ghost-blue"},{"x":76,"y":19,"type":"ghost-blue"}],"platforms":[{"x":1,"y":6,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":523,"upDown":false,"leftRight":true,"speed":0.15},{"x":37,"y":23,"width":5,"height":1,"ch":"Û","attr":523,"upDown":false,"leftRight":false,"speed":0.15}],"powerUps":[],"player":{"x":1,"y":2},"door":{"x":37,"y":19}}]